[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these pieces of clothing is worn on the head?", "correct_answer": "Fez", "incorrect_answers": ["Mitumba", "Koto", "Kiondo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The case of identical twins of different sex is extremely rare. The development of their gender starts 5 weeks after the moment of conceiving.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Under whose rule was the island of Cyprus when it was conquered by the Ottoman Empire in 1571?", "correct_answer": "Venice", "incorrect_answers": ["France", "Greece", "The Papal States"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The two main groups of students in the movie Grease 2 are The Pink Ladies and this boys group.", "correct_answer": "The T-Birds", "incorrect_answers": ["The T-Bones", "The T-Squares", "The T-Shirts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dustin Hoffman was in two movies that won the Best Picture Academy Award in the 1980-1989 period.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The fear of the fatal date is called this.", "correct_answer": "Paraskevidekatriaphobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Aphenphosmphobia", "Chronomentrophobia", "Coitophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) was formed in this year.", "correct_answer": "1949", "incorrect_answers": ["1945", "1941", "1950"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who were the two teenagers who were transported into various time periods in a series of movies?", "correct_answer": "Bill and Ted", "incorrect_answers": ["George and Henry", "Joe and Tom", "Archie and Reggie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This animal is the second most expensive for zoos to maintain after the Giant Panda.", "correct_answer": "Elephant", "incorrect_answers": ["Lion", "Giraffe", "Bear"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What country banned the movie Bruce Almighty due to pressure from religious groups?", "correct_answer": "Egypt", "incorrect_answers": ["Israel", "Libya", "Iran"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This island, also known as Formosa, is the largest island of the Republic of China.", "correct_answer": "Taiwan", "incorrect_answers": ["Matsu", "Penghu", "Honshu"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Scoville scale is used to measure the hotness of what?", "correct_answer": "Chilli peppers", "incorrect_answers": ["Magma", "Sun rays", "Internal combustion engines"]}]